THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
- Let's have one more drink.
- You had too much already.
6 YEARS AGO
No, you need to go home.
Hey, mister. Join me for a drink.
- They won't drink with me.
- Have you gone crazy?
- Stop it.
- Sorry.
- Go home.
- No.
- I'm fine. Let go of me.
- You sure?
The taxi's not here yet?
- It's...
- Let's go drink!
- What's wrong with you?
- What?
- Let go.
- It's coming.
- It's not here yet.
- It's here.
- Here it is.
- It's here?
- It's here.
- Darn it.
- Where are we going?
- Mapo-gu.
- For Mapo-gu, right?
- That's where you live.
- I live there?
- Yes.
- Okay, I'm fine. Let go.
- Okay.
Wait. Give me a moment.
- Darn it.
- What now?
- Here's 20,000 won for Seon-hyuk.
- Thank you.
And 20,000 won for Eun-tae.
- Take a taxi home.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Hey, I have no cash.
- Give me 10,000 won. I'm out.
- Give me yours.
- Mine?
- I'm all out.
- Bye!
- No, wait.
- Now we can afford another...
- We can't.
That hurt, you know. It really hurt.
- Hey, wait. My briefcase.
- Here you go.
This isn't mine. Give me mine.
Why are you so out of it?
Are you sure you two
won't go drinking without me?
- We won't. Bye.
- Are you sure?
- Bye. See you.
- I'm serious. Don't do that.
Take care!
That was so freaking hard.
It took us 30 minutes
to get him to go.
That's way faster than before.
He used to fall asleep on the ground.
Will you be like that
if you become a team leader?
Why?
Will you send me home
when I become a team leader?
I'll do exactly that tonight.
Hey, Gong...
- You. Follow me.
- What?
- Follow me.
- Why?
- Come with me.
- Where to?
Do you buy lottery tickets?
I've tried it a couple of times.
What's today's date?
It's April 27th,
and the time is 11...
It's 11:42 p.m.
Forty-two.
The last digit
of your employee number.
My employee number...
Oh, it's an eight.
Eight for you. Three for me.
LOTTO, PENSION LOTTERY, SCRATCH-OFF
The rest will be randomly generated.
- Sir.
- Yes?
- Two tickets with these numbers.
- Okay.
Thanks.
One for me, one for you.
Thank you.
Do you buy these often?
Whenever I see a stall.
Don't you?
I don't want to get my hopes up
when I'll never win, anyway.
Who cares if you never win?
Do you buy them
thinking you'll win when you won't?
Doesn't it feel like
this moment has more meaning now?
Work is always the same.
Life is boring.
Buying a lottery ticket
gives time some meaning.
That makes today worth celebrating.
That's why I buy them.
That's pretty romantic.
Don't fall for me.
You never know.
There are eight billion people
out there.
What's the probability
that we would ever meet?
I don't know.
One in 100 million?
No, one in 10 million.
I don't know, either.
But the chance of winning
the lottery is one in eight million.
Doesn't that mean
the chance of us meeting
is almost as good as the chance
that we'll win the lottery?
You and I happened to meet.
Who's to say we won't win?
I say it's possible.
If this is worth anything,
we're halving it, okay?
Let's go home now.
LOTTERY TICKETS
Where's my briefcase?
Oh, yes. Thank you.
EPISODE 5: WHEN NO ONE SAYS
WHAT THEY REALLY FEEL
HONGSUNG
INTERNATIONAL
Oh, my goodness.
Are you all here because of me?
You get that much?
So what is it?
Did you rush over anxiously
to apologize for causing a mess
or to clean it up?
Will it all be okay if I apologize?
Of course not, you punk.
What should I do, then?
I don't know.
What do you want me to do, Mr. Jang?
What are you even doing right now?
Should I stay here
wasting space and time
just waiting to be fired?
Is that what you think you do here?
You don't deserve to lead a team.
I wouldn't have promoted you
if I'd known you were like this.
I'm sorry
but I'm not here to apologize
or clean anything up.
You're not?
Then how about
you explain your actions?
Explain?
Did I do something wrong?
I can get why you tried to steal
one of our business partners.
Well, I don't get it,
but Ms. Park can, so I'll let it go.
You were there
when we signed on Mantua
so we can say you own some equity.
But if you want to leave,
leave alone.
Why poach our employees?
If Hongsung is a better company,
they'll choose to stay here.
If not, they'll come with me.
I can't force someone
to come with me.
The decision is theirs to make.
You sound so rational and reasonable.
Okay, then.
I'll respond just as rationally.
Do you think Hongsung won't retaliate
if you quit like this?
Oh, gosh...
Mr. Jang.
Do you think I have
some grudge against Hongsung?
Who, me?
I was loyal to Hongsung
for over a good decade.
If I could do my job
without having to quit, I'd stay.
If any Hongsung employee
wants to come with me
that's only because
they feel the same.
Let's be honest.
Hongsung doesn't treat people well.
I plan to do what Hongsung can't.
- Mr. Jeong.
- Yes?
Do you think you're any different?
You can't even manage your own team.
How can you start a company
that treats people well?
That's just nonsense.
That's for me to prove.
- Seon-hyuk.
- Yes?
Our industry isn't a massive ocean.
It's a tiny stream.
Do you think your company
will survive with us as an enemy?
Are you actually concerned about me?
Yes.
I'm really concerned
about the fool you are.
Thank you for your concern.
But today
I came here to ask you
not to scold the employees
that I offered a job to
because they did nothing wrong.
Will you do that for me?
Jeez...
I take it that you will
and excuse myself.
Thank you.
Hey, Gong.
Yes?
Lock down Mantua as soon as possible.
So that's why Mr. Jang came to Legal.
He asked to see
Mr. Jeong's employment contract.
To check
for the non-compete agreement.
Does that carry any weight?
It does legally,
but it's hard to enforce.
It's an awkward lawsuit
with no guarantee of winning.
Time will pass as the trial drags on,
and time will side with Mr. Jeong.
Do you know Ms. Park came by
a week before that?
- Did she?
- Yes.
She asked the same thing as Mr. Jang.
She wasn't going
to let it slide, either.
Of course not.
What he's doing is harming Hongsung.
The higher-ups
are scarier than you think.
By the way
do you know why Ms. Park
didn't make us take action?
No, why?
If we make a move,
so will the Audit Team.
Would you want to make things worse
if you were her?
I can't say for sure
but I think Mr. Jeong considered that
when he planned this.
I really don't know, though.
Should I say Mr. Jeong
is being clever
or pitiful?
I don't know, either.
I want to root for him
whatever the outcome
but he makes me want to put away
the pompoms and draw a sword.
A multi-brand shoe store?
Yes, it's a new project,
and it was rushed.
Are we doing it? How come?
I pulled something crazy.
If you were going to do that,
you should've given us a heads-up.
Do we have enough people to handle
Laknes and the shoe store?
Mantua will select the brands,
and Ms. Park will clear the finances.
Mr. Jang will help us deal
with the brands' head offices.
There shouldn't be
much actual work to do.
Mr. Gong.
Are we doing this
because of Mr. Jeong?
No.
We're doing it
because Hongsung needs us to.
The most important thing, then.
What's the budget?
That's only for the first order.
Future ones can reach ten million.
What do you think?
Do you think that's enough
to persuade Mantua?
It's a decent number.
The number's decent.
So what are you worried about?
The Mantua guys
aren't that reasonable.
I'm more worried
that you're close to Mr. Jeong.
What do you think?
Mr. Jang.
Did you forget this was my idea?
No.
I also know
you didn't want to do this.
I don't care about anything else.
It'll be a huge headache
if you can't close the deal
with this budget.
I'll close it.
Good.
Eun-tae.
This is work.
Don't forget that.
I won't.
22 HOURS TO LAKNES LAUNCH
Ms. Cha, I saw the revised version.
It looks great.
I saw the posts,
and they all look good.
- Oh, yes.
- Gang, Lee, and Park.
- They didn't post the product alone.
- Yes, thanks. Bye.
Oh, yes, hello.
- There are 30?
- Did you get what I sent?
- Did you open the whole box?
- Yes, about that.
The event that you proposed.
- Do you mind opening two more?
- Sorry for all the changes.
I'll take you out to eat
after the launch.
- Yes, please check.
- Bye.
Oh, yes.
- Thank you. Bye.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Sorry?
What are you doing?
We're taking a break.
Are you done?
Let's go.
12 HOURS TO LAKNES LAUNCH
9 HOURS TO LAKNES LAUNCH
- Ji-hye.
- Yes?
Watch your pace. This is a marathon.
Okay.
Hey, Gi-tae.
You're too slow.
Go at least half her speed.
This is a marathon, you see.
- What?
- You're the slowest, Mr. Yang.
Oh, Mr. Gong.
Come and take a seat.
Sorry I'm late.
Don't be. We just got started.
Where do I start?
Put these stickers on there.
Why did you join us? We could manage.
Laknes opens tomorrow.
- We have a final meeting too.
- Mr. Gong.
The banners are up on the Gangnam
and Sogong-dong stores.
We're halfway through
the influencer marketing.
We confirmed
the opening event and supply
and this bar code sticker job
is the last on the list.
We leave the rest to the heavens.
No one up there will help
stick the bar codes.
It's crucial that we finish this
by morning.
Heaven helps those
who help themselves.
He keeps spouting stuff like that.
- Come here. You need help.
- Sorry. I'll stop.
I'll do all of this.
- Sorry. I'll help.
- Hands off.
- Okay, fine. Let me.
- I'll do it all.
Excuse me.
- Where are you going?
- Leave my share to do later.
Hey, don't you think
he looks excited these days?
He does.
Good thinking.
Yes. Bye.
Korea?
Yes. Hongsung.
- Are they coming to discuss Jeong?
- Probably.
They won't come empty-handed.
They'll bring an armful.
Whatever they bring,
don't touch what's mine, okay?
You should know me by now.
I'm disappointed.
42 MINUTES TO LAKNES LAUNCH
Wait here.
- What time is it?
- It's 9:48 a.m.
No, wait.
We need to move two at once.
Okay.
That's it.
- Gi-tae.
- Let me.
We made it on time.
We can't say yet.
We're cutting it close.
Hey, Ji-hye.
- Two boxes?
- You can do it.
I told you to wait.
What?
Hurry up, Ji-hye.
Move it.
You barely made it.
I thought we'd lost you.
We came as soon as we could.
We were up all night.
It wasn't my idea to get the goods
so close to opening.
Oh, whatever. I deserve praise.
Forget the praise and drink this.
Thanks. I knew it was for us.
You redid the whole display wall.
You think we weren't working?
- Drink outside the store.
- I haven't even taken a sip.
- Mr. Gong.
- Yes.
Here's an iced coffee.
The mall is open. Get ready.
Is this the sound of footsteps?
Are they coming to Laknes?
Welcome. There's no need to run.
Stay close to the wall, please.
Take your time.
Please wait here.
Excuse me.
Bye then.
Mr. Gong, have a coffee.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Did you get some rest?
Well, yes. I'm rested up.
Good. We're going on a business trip.
Pardon?
You're coming with me to Italy.
- Am I going with you?
- Yes.
It's time you went
on a business trip.
Oh, okay. Got it.
Will this be your first trip there?
Yes, I've never been to Italy.
What a shame.
You're going to Italy,
but you won't get to see any of it.
- What?
- You'll see what I mean.
That's what business trips are like.
Okay.
MANTUA, ITALY
Everything here is limited edition.
Gi-tae?
Mr. Gong?
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
Why did you bring me on this trip?
You asked the same thing I did.
What?
From now on,
when you visit an Italian warehouse
don't be too surprised.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Mr. Sponza.
It's a pleasure for me too.
I booked a perfect restaurant.
Give me one minute.
I should've recorded that.
The negotiation is not over yet.
What?
There's no way Sponza
would drop it like this.
Try the coffee.
What do you mean
the shipment's withheld?
No, that can't be. Check again.
What? Hello?
Hello?
Damn it, what the heck?
The call cannot be connected.
Sponza, you rascal.
Emilio.
I told you, Sponza.
Don't touch what's mine.
I heard you.
That's why I'm asking for a favor.
I don't know how big
your Hongsung deal is
but I cannot cancel this shipment.
May I know the reason
you're refusing?
He speaks Italian?
I had no idea.
I'm still learning.
If I know why you're refusing,
perhaps I can help.
Okay. My daughter designed
the products in this shipment.
I wasn't a good father
since I divorced her mother.
This is the first ever order
my daughter got.
And you want me to cancel it? No way.
May I ask what the products are?
They're sunglasses.
Including the sunglasses
how much did Mr. Jeong
order in total?
About 900,000 euros.
I'm sorry?
- How did that happen?
- That's how things went.
I'll send you all the related info.
Can you set it up so I can report it
as soon as I get back?
I can get the papers in order,
but how did that happen?
I had to do it to seal the deal.
So you spent an extra 900,000 euros?
This is insane.
I'll explain when I get back.
Of course, you must explain, but...
- Do that for me.
- Hello?
Mr. Gong?
What's gotten into him?
- Did he get excited again?
- Yes.
What are you thinking, Mr. Gong?
We did things
the Hongsung way so far.
At least this time,
I'd like to do things my way.
Sorry?
The worst they can do is fire me.
What?
Mr. Gong!
MISSED CALL FROM
TEAM 4 MR. JEONG SEON-HYUK
Mr. Gong, take the taxi in front.
- Okay.
- Bye, then.
Good job. Get back safely.
Can you open the trunk for me?
Mr. Gong.
I learned a lot on this trip.
Thank you.
You really are just like me.
What?
Never mind. See you tomorrow.
Okay. Goodbye.
Hey, there.
Why are you so down?
A CEO can't let something like this
get to him.
Do I look down?
Hongsung is scary.
I'm sure you expected this.
I didn't think they'd go this far.
Do you blame me?
I blame myself.
I took you to Mantua.
Your eyes bugged out
when you saw the warehouse.
I taught the clueless kid everything
and this is what he does to me.
You told me then
that I shouldn't act too surprised
in the warehouse.
Did I?
Did I go too far?
Even if I did go too far
do you think I deserve this?
The multi-brand shoe store.
Was that your idea or Hongsung's?
It was my idea.
Hongsung agreed.
I see.
Mr. Jeong.
If I import the product,
will you buy from us?
- What?
- But it will be
a bit more expensive
than what Mantua asked for.
- What are you saying?
- It's as you heard.
You can't deal directly
with Mantua ever again.
If you want their product,
you must buy it from Hongsung.
The shipment is on its way.
You can come to Hongsung this week
to sign the contract.
I'll persuade them.
Are you throwing me a lifeline?
I should go.
Hello.
Explain.
There was one guy who refused
to cancel his deal with Mr. Jeong.
- Hey.
- She's the director.
Get straight to the point.
I didn't want to destroy Mr. Jeong.
What about us, then?
And the other team leaders.
Did we want to destroy him?
I didn't think anyone did.
- Jeez.
- The shipment Mr. Jeong ordered
will count as sales from our side.
At the same time, I believe
it serves as a warning to someone
who resigned in an abnormal manner.
Are you saying
it works out for everyone?
Yes, that's what I believe.
So you went over
the agreed budget by 30%.
Even if the order
can be counted as sales
do you think it's okay
to make that decision on your own
as team leader?
What if I don't sign off on this?
I represented Hongsung
to make a deal.
I believe this is
the best possible result.
Okay.
It's on me for sending you to Mantua.
For the time being,
report to me directly
whenever your team places an order.
Ask for approval before you spend
even a single won.
Yes, ma'am.
There's something you got wrong.
Do you think Mr. Jeong
will be grateful for what you did?
Is Mr. Son late again today?
This place is a total mess.
Gi-tae.
(Check your phone.)
OUR DEEPEST CONDOLENCES
HONGSUNG INTERNATIONAL
I heard he was ill for a long time.
He wasn't in pain when he passed.
You should've told us.
It's not something to brag about.
I should've looked out for you.
- Sorry.
- Don't be.
CONDOLENCE MONEY BOX
Thanks for coming.
The deceased's son is present.
You can go on in.
Thanks for coming.
Isn't work an interesting place?
They argue all the time
but they all help out
when things like this happen.
Yes, I guess that keeps us going.
I heard you'll be supplying
Mr. Jeong's company.
Yes, that's the plan.
You did the right thing.
Do you really think so?
He used to be family.
We all know what happened.
Hang on. Is that Mr. Jeong?
BAEKSAN UNIVERSITY FUNERAL HALL
- Hello.
- Hi, it's been a while.
Hello.
- Let's go inside.
- Not me.
I was going to pass you this.
Gift the money for me.
You came all the way. Go and say hi.
I shouldn't show myself.
Take the envelope.
CONDOLENCE MONEY
I'm leaving. Look after him.
- Are you driving for Hongsung?
- Yes, Hongsung International.
Where are the others?
I'm the only one. Why?
What are you on about?
All those are for Hongsung.
- That's all for Hongsung?
- Yes.
- It can't be.
- I'm serious. It's all theirs.
Call someone to check.
- Can I have more soju?
- More soju?
- Yes.
- Just a moment. Ji-hye?
Ji-hye.
I'll get it for you right away.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
LEE MIN-HO, HONGSUNG DISTRIBUTION
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
6 YEARS AGO
- Hello, Mr. Jang.
- Hi.
Did you have a drink last night?
Yes, I did.
How much did you drink?
An effing crazy amount.
Then I'll make you
a nice cup of hot honey tea.
Thanks so much.
Darn it.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Do you buy lottery tickets?
Sometimes.
Don't buy them sometimes.
Buy one every week.
We're both office workers.
This is our only hope.
LOTTO
5270TH DRAWING
Hey.
You won something?
SORRY, YOU DID NOT WIN
Of course, I'm damn unlucky.
Oh, whatever.
Cheer up, Mr. Jang.
STAFF GONG EUN-TAE
- We're having jjamppong for lunch.
- Thank you.
- Mr. Jang has a hangover?
- Yes, he drank an effing lot.
Did you check your lottery ticket?
We halve the winnings, okay?
It'll be a dud. Did you check?
I will now.
CONGRATULATIONS
TOTAL WINNINGS: 50,000 WON
- It's a dud, right?
- What?
Yeah. Shoot.
Of course, I'm damn unlucky.
It's hard to win this thing.
Subtitles by Jennifer Jean Lim